sgxnifty.org 2014-06-25

# SGX Nifty | Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information through our web site. "Personal Information" means information that would allow a party to contact you, including, for example, your full name, address, telephone number, or email address.  
**Submitted Information**

We collect Personal Information about you when you submit information or requests to us (through this website or otherwise). We use your submitted information to send you emails that you have requested, to send your job application and resume to the applicable third party when you apply to certain jobs on our web site, to improve your job search experience on our web site, and for administrative purposes (such as to notify you about changes to this Privacy Policy). In emails we send you, we provide a method to unsubscribe from future emails.  
**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, SGX Nifty makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
SGX Nifty does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. **DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
» Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on SGX Nifty.  
» Google�s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to SGX Nifty and other sites on the Internet.  
» Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense, Yahoo Contextual Ads, Media.net, Commission Junction, Adbrite, Clickbank, Azoogle, Chitika, Linkshare, Amazon, Kontera and others which may be included from time to time.  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on SGX Nifty send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
**SGX Nifty has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.**  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.   
SGX Nifty�s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
**_If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites._**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us here.  
At SGX Nifty, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by SGX Nifty and how it is used.

**Data Content**  
The data contained in SGX Nifty's search results, or linked from those results, have been created by people over whom SGX Nifty exercises no control. SGX Nifty's data search results are indexed in an automated manner and SGX Nifty does not screen the data. SGX Nifty assumes no responsibility for the content of any data listing or website that is either included in SGX Nifty's search results or linked to by SGX Nifty.com.   
**Forums**  
The SGX Nifty message boards, other forums as well as other opportunities to post hosted by SGX Nifty and its designees (collectively, the "Forums") are designed to help readers obtain career and company information and discuss ways to make career decisions. This information is provided by outside contributors, many of whom use anonymous screen names. They may occasionally post messages or make statements that are misleading, deceptive, or downright wrong. SGX Nifty does not endorse and is not responsible for any opinion, advice, information, or statement made or displayed on the Forums by third parties.   
Users of the Forums must not post content or information that is unlawful, fraudulent, threatening, abusive, libelous, defamatory, obscene or otherwise objectionable or that contains sexual, ethnic or racial or other discriminating slurs, or material which contains no relevant or constructive content or which goes beyond profanity into obscenity or abhorrence. Users are also prohibited from posting any proprietary information, trade secrets or confidential information. Users may not post any advertisements, solicitations, chain letters, pyramid schemes, investment opportunities, or other unsolicited commercial communication (except as otherwise expressly permitted by us), or engage in spamming or flooding.  
Although SGX Nifty has no obligation to do so, SGX Nifty may monitor messages posted on its Forums and reserves the right to delete portions of or entire posts which violate the above rules, messages or topics that are unrelated to the specific message board on which they are posted, and advertisements, recruiting or other commercial messages. If you believe a message violates our policies, please contact SGX Nifty immediately at here so that we can consider its editing or removal. SGX Nifty reserves the right to disclose such materials and the circumstances surrounding their transmission to any third party in order to operate its site properly; to protect itself, its partners and its visitors; and to comply with legal obligations or governmental requests.  
**Ownership and Rights to Use Materials**  
SGX Nifty does not claim ownership of information, data, text or other materials submitted by third parties (collectively, "Materials"). However, by posting Materials to any area of the SGX Nifty website, you grant SGX Nifty and its designees a worldwide, royalty-free, non-exclusive perpetual, irrevocable and fully sub-licensable license to use, distribute, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, publicly perform and publicly display such Materials (in whole or in part) and to incorporate such Materials into other works in any format or medium now known or later developed. We shall not be liable for any use or disclosure of any Materials.  
**Registration**  
Some areas of the SGX Nifty service require you to register as a member. If you register to become a member, you agree to (a) provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by our registration form (including your email address) and (b) will be responsible for the confidentiality and use of your username and password and agree not to transfer or resell your use of or access to the Site to any third party.   
**Change In Service and Terms**  
SGX Nifty may modify or terminate the SGX Nifty Services from time to time, for any reason, and without notice. SGX Nifty reserves the right to modify these Terms of Service from time to time without notice.
